<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BarQuest</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_tut_title">Welcome to BarQuest</string>

    <string name="home_tut_msg">Welcome to BarQuest, a world of adventure, danger and code!\n\n
                        You are a simple adventurer on a quest to become stronger, and on your journey will face perilous dangers in the form of monsters.\n\n
                        To begin your journey click “SCAN”
    </string>

    <string name="scan_tut_title">
        Scanning
    </string>

    <string name="scan_tut_msg">
        In order to find monsters you must scan a barcode or QR Code \n\n
        Make sure to line up the scan line with the code you are scanning
    </string>

    <string name="battle_tut_title">
        Battling Monsters
    </string>

    <string name="battle_tut_msg">
        To fight a monster click the attack button \n\n
        To heal or boost your stats temporarily use an item \n\n
        To run away click flee, but be warned you won’t always get away \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="char_tut_title">
        Checking Your Character
    </string>

    <string name="char_tut_msg">
        This screen shows your character stats and your progress on your adventure
    </string>

    <string name="levelUp_tut_title">
        Congrats You Leveled Up!
    </string>

    <string name="levelUp_tut_msg">
        As you fight monsters and gain experience you will level up and increase your stats \n\n
        Every 100 experience points your level will increase
    </string>

    <string name="inventory_tut_title">
        Inventory
    </string>

    <string name="inventory_tut_msg">
        Here you can check your items and change your equipped weapon \n\n
        Weapons have differing reaches providing a bonus damage modifier. Long > Mid > Close > Long \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="shop_tut_title">
        Shopping Spree!
    </string>

    <string name="shop_tut_msg">
       Friendly shopkeeps will buy your loot and sell you new items \n\n
        Check back often as the wares change from time to time  \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="quest_tut_title">
        Questing!
    </string>

    <string name="quest_tut_msg">
        Here you can check your progress on your quests.
        Completing quests will advance your character, get new and rare items and give clues on your journey
    </string>
</resources>

